{
	"results": [
		{
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"datatype": "text",
			"question": "In the developer's opinion, Sass is way better than CSS, jQuery beats vanilla DOM manipulation any day, and TypeScript is only script.",
			"type": "boolean",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": ["False"],
			"credit": "single",
			"case": ["dev", "boolean", "easy"]
		},
		{
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"datatype": "text",
			"question": "What percentage should be added to 40 to make it 50?",
			"type": "multiple",
			"correct_answer": "25%",
			"incorrect_answers": ["15%", "75%", "80%"],
			"credit": "single",
			"case": ["dev", "multiple", "text", "single"]
		},
		{
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"datatype": "text",
			"question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it's entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
			"type": "boolean",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": ["True"],
			"credit": "single",
			"case": ["dev", "boolean", "medium"]
		},
		{
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"datatype": "text",
			"question": "If x^2 = 100, what are the possible values for x?",
			"type": "multiple",
			"correct_answer": ["10", "-10", "0-(10i)^2"],
			"incorrect_answers": ["(10i)^2"],
			"credit": "partial",
			"case": ["dev", "multiple", "text", "partial"]
		},
		{
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"datatype": "text",
			"question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
			"type": "boolean",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": ["False"],
			"credit": "single",
			"case": ["dev", "boolean", "hard"]
		},
		{
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"datatype": "link",
			"question": "Which of the URLs link to a page not found?",
			"type": "multiple",
			"correct_answer": "https://jedi.mycohort.download/second-language/week-24/day-3/",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"https://jedi.mycohort.download/coding-challenges#reverseupcasestring",
				"www.mycohort.com",
				"https://jedi.mycohort.download/frontend-fundamentals/week-3/day-3/labs/my-developer-skills-lab/"
			],
			"hint": "Familiarize yourself with the curriculum! Also, mycohort is currently for sale by HugeDomains, but nonetheless is a valid endpoint.",
			"credit": "single",
			"case": ["dev", "multiple", "link"]
		},
		{
			"category": "General%20Knowledge",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The%20Lego%20Group%20was%20founded%20in%201932.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": ["False"],
			"case": ["otdb", "boolean", "easy"]
		},
		{
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"datatype": "img",
			"question": "Whose personal GitHub account has the highest contribution count over the last year?",
			"type": "multiple",
			"correct_answer": "https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/52634838?s=460&u=aa05b8fcee5a38a55b56857aa379dce4887b25ca&v=4",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/58452223?s=460&u=79de1747e237fcac827d9842a93b638cc21802d7&v=4",
				"https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/66440550?s=460&u=8efbed4567f07197b4ad49e0121f04173e2251f1&v=4",
				"https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/936204?s=460&u=1c75ba3339476e753d3a6f8f067b1057220a4171&v=4",
				"https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/17891125?s=460&u=abf4021515edef127878f03b5d5ccb3c6fc31399&v=4"
			],
			"hint": "Stalk them for yourself and see!",
			"credit": "single",
			"case": ["dev", "multiple", "img"]
		},
		{
			"category": "General%20Knowledge",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "The%20sum%20of%20all%20the%20numbers%20on%20a%20roulette%20wheel%20is%20666.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": ["False"],
			"case": ["otdb", "boolean", "medium"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Politics",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "How%20many%20people%20are%20in%20the%20U.S.%20House%20of%20Representatives%3F",
			"correct_answer": "435",
			"incorrect_answers": ["260", "415", "50"],
			"case": ["otdb", "multiple", "easy"]
		},
		{
			"category": "General%20Knowledge",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "hard",
			"question": "Spoon%20theory%20is%20a%20theory%2C%20utilizing%20%22Spoons%22%20as%20a%20metaphor%20for%20energy%20they%20can%20use%20in%20a%20day.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": ["False"],
			"case": ["otdb", "boolean", "hard"]
		}
	]
}
